easytobook.com 2012-06-11

# 

Easytobook respects the privacy of all our customers and therefore all your personal data will be attended to with the highest confidentiality.

In order to offer you the fastest and easiest service, we do request your personal data upon booking with us. Your personal data will only be shared with your chosen hotel venue. Easytobook.com will never share your personal data to other parties than your chosen hotel venue, except if the Dutch government obliges us to do so.

In order to make a booking, we have to forward your personal data to your chosen accommodation. The accommodation uses your contact details to identify you upon arrival at their venue or to contact you in case of changes in your booking.

Easytobook.com would like to emphasize that our Privacy Statement is in accordance with the European Law for Personal data protection. 

**Cookie Statement:**  
Easytobook.com makes use of cookies; small simple text files that are stored on your hard drive or computer. These files do not harm your computer in any way. The cookies can never lead back to any personal information and do not contain your name or e-mail address; they are just stored under a number that recognizes your computer.  
Cookies are used to trace which information, products or services interest you, so more personal advertisement can be directed at you, on this and other websites. They can also save your set preferences for a specific site or service for your convenience.  
At any time, you can set your cookies from your browser settings. You can switch them off totally, or be warned when a website wants to set a cookie for you.

* * *

**In order to guarantee bookings of our customers at hotel venues, we require the following personal data:**

  * First name of the guest
  * Last name of the guest
  * Country
  * Contact telephone number
  * Email Address
  * Card details

* * *

Your card details: 

Easytobook.com uses your card details to guarantee the booking, some deals however require prepayment at the time of booking. The conditions can be found in the descriptions of the hotel and they are shown in the booking process as well.

The website of easytobook.com is secured with the SSL technology (Secure Socket Layer). By using this technology your personal data and card details will be encrypted before all information will be sent to our secure server.

To protect our customers, our server and network are protected with firewalls and other anti-hacker technologies. Therefore we can guarantee our customers that providing us with your card details are safe and secure.

Rest assured, easytobook.com will not sell your personal information. You can count on us to keep your credit card information secure and always protect your privacy.

* * *

SSL Technology 

The SSL encryption process converts the information you enter into bits of code which are securely transmitted over the Internet when you submit your Booking Form. This scrambled data cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.  
Once the encrypted data is received by our secure server, it is translated back into its original form so that our systems can read and process it. Your credit card information is not transmitted over the Internet again.

* * *

Book by telephone 

If you prefer to give your credit card details over the telephone, you can call our Customer Service Team with your credit card information and booking details, and we will process the booking for you. Call +31 20 5313300

See full list of frequently asked questions (FAQ).

* * *

Email correspondence from easytobook.com:

After you have processed your booking on our website, we will send you a confirmation email to confirm your booking with us. It is not necessary to present your booking confirmation at the hotel. Your reference at the hotel is your leading guest name.

To develop our booking service, we may send you after sales emails. If you do not appreciate such emails you can easily opt out by clicking on the Preferences link on the top of our Newsletter. Alternatively you can send an email to support@ematters.nl to unsubscribe.

Should you have any questions or remarks about our privacy statement, please contact at [ customercare@easytobook.com ](mailto:customercare@easytobook.com) or by telephone on +31 20 531 33 00.  
See full list of frequently asked questions (FAQ).
